<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>An implementation of a secret sharing scheme.</title>
    <link>https://itslab-kyushu.github.io/sss/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on An implementation of a secret sharing scheme.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://itslab-kyushu.github.io/sss/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Command line usage</title>
      <link>https://itslab-kyushu.github.io/sss/cli/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://itslab-kyushu.github.io/sss/cli/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;The secret sharing scheme this command provides is a simple
&lt;a href=&#34;http://dx.doi.org/10.1007/978-3-642-20901-7_2&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;k&lt;/em&gt;-out-of-&lt;em&gt;n&lt;/em&gt; threshold secret sharing&lt;/a&gt;,
which means totally &lt;em&gt;n&lt;/em&gt; shares will be made from one secret file,
and you need to at least &lt;em&gt;k&lt;/em&gt; shares to reconstruct the secret.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;client-usage&#34;&gt;Client Usage&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The client application provides two way to run the threshold Secret Sharing
scheme (SSS).
One of them is local mode, which stores shares into a local file system.
The other one is remote mode, which stores shares into servers provided the
server command.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;local-mode&#34;&gt;Local mode&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The local mode provides two sub commands, distribute and reconstruct.
Distribute command reads a file and creates a set of shares,
on the other hand, reconstruct command reads a set of shares and reconstructs
the original file.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;distribute&#34;&gt;Distribute&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ sss local distribute &amp;lt;file&amp;gt; &amp;lt;number of shares&amp;gt; &amp;lt;threshold&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This command produces share files and the file name of i-th share has &lt;code&gt;.i.xz&lt;/code&gt;
as the suffix.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This command also takes an optional flag &lt;code&gt;--chunk&lt;/code&gt; to specify the byte size of
each chunk.
The given secret file is divided to chunks based on this size and distributed
in shares.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;reconstruct&#34;&gt;Reconstruct&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ sss local reconstruct &amp;lt;file&amp;gt;...
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It produces a file based on the given share&amp;rsquo;s file name by removing the above
suffix.
For example, if the names of share files are &lt;code&gt;sample.txt.1.xz&lt;/code&gt;,
&lt;code&gt;sample.txt.2.xz&lt;/code&gt;, &amp;hellip;, then the default file name of the reconstructed secret
will be &lt;code&gt;sample.txt&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can use &lt;code&gt;--output&lt;/code&gt; flag to use another file name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;remote-mode&#34;&gt;Remote mode&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remote mode provides four sub command: get, put, delete, and list.
All commands take a YAML based server configuration file.
The format is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;servers:
  - address: 192.168.0.1
    port: 13009
  - address: 192.168.0.2
    port: 13009
  - address: 192.168.1.1
    port: 13009
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The above example defines three servers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The get command gathers shares from the servers defined the configuration file,
and put command distributes shares to the servers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The default name of the configuration file is &lt;code&gt;sss.yml&lt;/code&gt; but you can set another
name via &lt;code&gt;--config&lt;/code&gt; flag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;get&#34;&gt;Get&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;sss remote get --config sss.yml --output result.dat &amp;lt;file name&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Get command gathers shares associated with the given file name from the servers
defined in the configuration file, and then reconstructs and stores them as
the given file name via &lt;code&gt;--output&lt;/code&gt; flag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If &lt;code&gt;--config&lt;/code&gt; flag is omitted, &lt;code&gt;sss.yml&lt;/code&gt; is used, and if &lt;code&gt;--output&lt;/code&gt; flag is
omitted, &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;file name&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; is used.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To find available file names, use list command.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The number of groups and the number of total servers must be greater then or
equal to the group threshold and the data threshold, which are given when those
shares were created.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;put&#34;&gt;Put&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;sss remote put --config sss.yml &amp;lt;file&amp;gt; &amp;lt;threshold&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Put command reads the given file and runs distribute procedure to create shares.
The threshold is a parameter of SSS.
The number of total shares are as same as defined in the server configuration
file.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If &lt;code&gt;--config&lt;/code&gt; flag is omitted, &lt;code&gt;sss.yml&lt;/code&gt; is used.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Put command also takes &lt;code&gt;--chunk&lt;/code&gt; flag to set the byte size of each chunk.
The default value is 256.
The distribute procedure creates a finite filed Z/pZ, where p is a prime number
which has chunk size + 1 bit length.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;delete&#34;&gt;Delete&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;sss remote delete --config sss.yml &amp;lt;file name&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Delete command deletes all shares associated with the given file name from all
servers defined in the configuration file.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If &lt;code&gt;--config&lt;/code&gt; flag is omitted, &lt;code&gt;sss.yml&lt;/code&gt; is used.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;list&#34;&gt;List&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;sss remote list --config sss.yml
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;List command shows all file names stored in the servers.
If &lt;code&gt;--config&lt;/code&gt; flag is omitted, &lt;code&gt;sss.yml&lt;/code&gt; is used.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;server-usage&#34;&gt;Server Usage&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The server application runs a simple data store service using SSS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It takes three flags,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;--port&lt;/code&gt;: the port number the server will listen,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;--root&lt;/code&gt;: the document root path to store uploaded shares,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;--no-compress&lt;/code&gt;: if set, all shares will be stored without compression.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If those flags are omitted, default values are used.
Thus, you can start a server by just run &lt;code&gt;sss-server&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>API Reference</title>
      <link>https://itslab-kyushu.github.io/sss/api/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://itslab-kyushu.github.io/sss/api/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;This software provides package &lt;code&gt;github.com/itslab-kyushu/sss/sss&lt;/code&gt;.
This package implements Distribute and Reconstruct functions, which execute
distribute and reconstruct procedures defined in a Secret Sharing scheme.
It also provides useful structures, Field and Polynomial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This page explains a base usage of those functions.
See &lt;a href=&#34;https://godoc.org/github.com/itslab-kyushu/sss/sss&#34;&gt;godoc&lt;/a&gt; for the detailed
information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;distribute&#34;&gt;Distribute&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Distribute function takes secret, chunk size, the total number of shares,
and minimum number of shares to reconstruct the secret, in this order,
and returns a slice of shares.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following example reads a file, creates shares and stores them in JSON
format.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-go&#34;&gt;secret, err := ioutil.ReadFile(&amp;quot;secret-file&amp;quot;)
if err != nil {
  return err
}

shares, err := sss.Distribute(secret, chunksize, totalShares, threshold)
if err != nil {
  return err
}

for i, s := range shares {
  data, err := json.Marshal(s)
  if err != nil {
    return err
  }
  filename := fmt.Sprintf(&amp;quot;%s.%d.json&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;share-&amp;quot;, i)
  if err = ioutil.WriteFile(filename, data, 0644); err != nil {
    return err
  }
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;reconstruct&#34;&gt;Reconstruct&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reconstruct takes a slice of shares and returns the secret in a slice of bytes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The following example reads a set of share files, reconstruct the secret, and
writes it to a file.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-go&#34;&gt;// shares is a slice of file names of shares.
shares := make([]sss.Share, len(shares))
for i, f := range shares {

  data, err := ioutil.ReadFile(f)
  if err != nil {
    return err
  }

  if err = json.Unmarshal(data, &amp;amp;shares[i]); err != nil {
    return err
  }

}

secret, err := sss.Reconstruct(shares)
if err != nil {
  return err
}
return ioutil.WriteFile(&amp;quot;secret-file&amp;quot;, secret, 0644)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Licenses</title>
      <link>https://itslab-kyushu.github.io/sss/licenses/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://itslab-kyushu.github.io/sss/licenses/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;This software is released under the GPLv3.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright &amp;copy; 2017 Junpei Kawamoto&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
(at your option) any later version.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
along with this program.  If not, see &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.gnu.org/licenses/&#34;&gt;http://www.gnu.org/licenses/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;notices-for-libraries&#34;&gt;Notices for libraries&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This software uses the following open source libraries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;cli-https-github-com-urfave-cli&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/urfave/cli&#34;&gt;cli&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright &amp;copy; 2016 Jeremy Saenz &amp;amp; Contributors&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Licensed under the MIT License.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
copies or substantial portions of the Software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &amp;ldquo;AS IS&amp;rdquo;, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
SOFTWARE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;go-support-for-protocol-buffers-https-github-com-golang-protobuf&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/golang/protobuf&#34;&gt;Go support for Protocol Buffers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright 2010 The Go Authors.  All rights reserved.
&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/golang/protobuf&#34;&gt;https://github.com/golang/protobuf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are
met:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;* Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
    * Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above
copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer
in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the
distribution.
    * Neither the name of Google Inc. nor the names of its
contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from
this software without specific prior written permission.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS
&amp;ldquo;AS IS&amp;rdquo; AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR
A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT
OWNER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL,
SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE,
DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY
THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT
(INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE
OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;grpc-go-https-github-com-grpc-grpc-go&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grpc/grpc-go&#34;&gt;gRPC-Go&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright 2014, Google Inc.
All rights reserved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are
met:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;* Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
    * Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above
copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer
in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the
distribution.
    * Neither the name of Google Inc. nor the names of its
contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from
this software without specific prior written permission.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS
&amp;ldquo;AS IS&amp;rdquo; AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR
A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT
OWNER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL,
SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE,
DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY
THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT
(INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE
OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;pb-https-github-com-cheggaaa-pb&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cheggaaa/pb&#34;&gt;pb&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright &amp;copy; 2012-2015, Sergey Cherepanov&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All rights reserved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification,
are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this
list of conditions and the following disclaimer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this
list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or
other materials provided with the distribution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Neither the name of the author nor the names of its contributors may be used
to endorse or promote products derived from this software without specific
prior written permission.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS &amp;ldquo;AS IS&amp;rdquo; AND
ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED
WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE
DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT HOLDER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR
ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES
(INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS
OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY
THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING
NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN
IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;package-xz-https-github-com-ulikunitz-xz&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ulikunitz/xz&#34;&gt;Package xz&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright &amp;copy; 2014-2016  Ulrich Kunitz
All rights reserved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this
list of conditions and the following disclaimer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice,
this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation
and/or other materials provided with the distribution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My name, Ulrich Kunitz, may not be used to endorse or promote products
derived from this software without specific prior written permission.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS &amp;ldquo;AS IS&amp;rdquo;
AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE
IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE
DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT HOLDER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE
FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL
DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR
SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER
CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY,
OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE
OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;yaml-support-for-the-go-language-https-github-com-go-yaml-yaml&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/go-yaml/yaml&#34;&gt;YAML support for the Go language&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright 2011-2016 Canonical Ltd.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the &amp;ldquo;License&amp;rdquo;);
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0&#34;&gt;http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an &amp;ldquo;AS IS&amp;rdquo; BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Implementation of Secret Sharing</title>
      <link>https://itslab-kyushu.github.io/sss/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://itslab-kyushu.github.io/sss/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gnu.org/copyleft/gpl.html&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://img.shields.io/badge/license-GPLv3-blue.svg&#34; alt=&#34;GPLv3&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://travis-ci.org/itslab-kyushu/sss&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://travis-ci.org/itslab-kyushu/sss.svg?branch=master&#34; alt=&#34;Build Status&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/itslab-kyushu/sss/releases/tag/v0.3.0&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://img.shields.io/badge/release-0.3.0-brightgreen.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Release&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This software provides both a &lt;a href=&#34;https://golang.org/&#34;&gt;GO&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://godoc.org/github.com/itslab-kyushu/sss/sss&#34;&gt;library&lt;/a&gt; implementing
a Secret Sharing scheme and a command line tool which distributes and
reconstructs your secret files.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;installation&#34;&gt;Installation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are only interested in our secret sharing library for Go,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-sh&#34;&gt;$ go get -d github.com/itslab-kyushu/sss
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in our server/client application,
compiled binaries of them are available on
&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/itslab-kyushu/sss/releases&#34;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;.
After downloading a binary to your environment, decompress and put it in a path
included in $PATH.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re a &lt;a href=&#34;http://brew.sh/&#34;&gt;Homebrew&lt;/a&gt; user,
you can install the client application by&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-sh&#34;&gt;$ brew tap itslab-kyushu/sss
$ brew install sss
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can also compile by yourself.
First, you need to download the code base:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ git clone https://github.com/itslab-kyushu/sss $GOPATH/src/itslab-kyushu/sss
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, build client command &lt;code&gt;sss&lt;/code&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ cd $GOPATH/src/itslab-kyushu/sss/client
$ go get -d -t -v .
$ go build -o sss
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and build server command &lt;code&gt;sss-server&lt;/code&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ cd $GOPATH/src/itslab-kyushu/sss/server
$ go get -d -t -v .
$ go build -o sss-server
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To build both commands, &lt;a href=&#34;https://golang.org/&#34;&gt;Go&lt;/a&gt; &amp;gt; 1.7.4 is required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;license&#34;&gt;License&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This software is released under The GNU General Public License Version 3,
see &lt;a href=&#34;./licenses/&#34;&gt;license&lt;/a&gt; for more detail.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>